# **VU THI PHUONG**

Le Loi, Ngo Quyen District, Hai Phong City | Mob: 0984 - 914 - 881 | Email: phuongduoc01@gmail.com

## **Professional Summary**

Working professionally for a year as a Medical Representative with consistently being at the top of the sale chart. My main focus is on the best client-oriented service where teamwork, communication, persuasion, organizational skills highly excel at. I believe being diligence, open-minded and enthusiastic on the needs of customers just as much as mine brings the best experience to customers.

#### **Career Goals**

Being able to fulfill my working tasks well to contribute to the development of the company and carry out extra tasks to challenge myself in a less uncomfortable situations to develop my experiences and sharpen my skills. Seeing myself as one of the best medical representatives in 2 months and senior/manager position within 5 years.

#### **Professional Experience**

2017 - Current Zuellig Pharma Vietnam Co., Ltd.

### Medical Representative

Take the responsible for working in some department in Bach Mai Hospital:

- Vietnam National Heart Institute
- Respiratory Center
- Emergency
- 4 another departments

And National Otorhinolaryngology Hospital of Vietnam; Hoe Nhai Hospital; Dong Do Hospital; National Hospital of Obstetrics and Gynecology

#### Detailed Work

- Built up and maintain relationship with KOLs, expand new business
- Follow up and resolve issues related to tender, quotation, customer complaint and business action of competitor...in field
- Make marketing plans in my business: group presentation, sponsorship and build up the strategy...

Becoming the best seller of the 1st quarter with 163%

Feb 2017 NIPRO Pharma Vietnam Co., Ltd.

Internship

2015 - 2017 DOTRAN Vietnam LLC

Saleman

2013 - 2017 The 4th Asian Association of Schools of Pharmacy Deans Forum

The 13th Asian Conference on Clinical Pharmacy

Volunteer

#### **Education and Awards**

2012 - 2017 Haiphong University of Medicine and Pharmacy

BSc Pharmaceutics, Standard Program

Grade: Credit 7.67

2015 - 2016 NIPRO Pharma Vietnam Co., Ltd

Scholarship

06/2015 Haiphong University of Medicine and Pharmacy

Scholarship for Excellent student

#### Skills

